inetzeal.com 2007-10-25

# iNetZeal.com - Privacy Policy

| 

    Navigation  
  
---  
|  |   

 BookMark Us!  
  
|  |   

 BookMark Us To Your Favorite Social Bookmarking Sites. :)  
  
  Testimonials  
  
|  |   
  
"the Google ranking for my 5 important keywords had raised A LOT. What I took from iNetZeal was a package service and Manish gave me a sweet discounted price. Now I am going to buy another service from iNetZeal again, hope this works as good as the last one. Especially thank Manish and I would like to recommend this service to people around me"... **Allen Lee.**  
   (Read more comments about our directory submit service  [ here](http://directory-submission.inetzeal.com/testimonials.htm) )  
  
| 

 iNetZeal Privacy Policy.  
  
---  

Inetzeal.com Privacy Policy 

Inetzeal reserves the right to alter this policy at any time, in whole or in part. This policy outlines Inetzeal's use of personal information that is collected from visitors when they use a website which is part of the Inetzeal Network - including inetzeal.com any sub-domains of inetzeal.com. 

Use of Cookies 

A cookie is a short text file that is downloaded to your computer which provides information as to the pages you have visited on our site. This practice is widely used on major websites as a means of profiling website visitors in an attempt to tailor the content that is delivered to them based on their preferences. For example, if you generally visit a particular section of our website, upon visiting our site, it is possible for Inetzeal to make that information more prominent to you throughout. Cookies are used by Inetzeal as a means of improving user-experience on our sites. It is possible to set your browser to reject cookies, however it is also likely that this could alter Inetzeal's ability to provide a seamless user experience. 

Removal Of Pre-Existing Information 

Should you wish to have pre-existing information removed from our records then please contact us using the contact details provided below. Inetzeal aim to respond to all requests of this nature in a timely manner. 

Further Information 

Should you require further information about Inetzeal's privacy policy, you can write to us, or email us, using the information provided below. 

Info@inetzeal.com  
5-Second Floor, Diwaliba Chambers, Near ICICI Bank, Mota Bazar, V V Nagar - 388120, India,  
Contact: 001-3203100670
